<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<templates xml:space="preserve">
    <t t-name="InstructionPage">
        <div>
        	<img src='/routesms/static/src/img/Auction-8.jpg' width="920" height="420" /> 
        	<h1 class="partner_auction_header">Welcome to our Online Auction.</h1>
			<div class="partner_auction_para">        	
	        	<p  >We are pleased to announce our enhanced services of conducting timed online auctions for partners.</p>
	        	<br></br>
	        	<pre >What is a timed auction?
	A timed auction is an internet only bidding system, where all items are partners/customers with 
	detailed descriptions. Bidders bid online for items of interest to them.
	The auction lasts for 5 days, and auctioneer(s) can regularly check on the status of their bids.
	At the conclusion of the bid, winning bidders are automatically contacted by <i>accounts department</i>
	and notified via email after swapping partner to winner bidders. 
	        	</pre>

	        	<pre >How does it work?
	STEP 1 :
	* There will be total 8phases where 500 partners will be released for auction every week.
	* To initiate go to Sale-> Bid On Partners -> Partner Auction
	* Choose the partners/customers who would like to bid
	* Every phase will be timed out in 5days.
	* There is no limit on bid, you can bid as many partners as per interest
	* More than 1 user can bid on same partner.
	
	        	</pre>	        	
	        	<img src='/routesms/static/src/img/partner aution list.png' class="partner_auction_image" />
	        	
	        	<pre>
	STEP 2 :
	* Find partner from list and hit bid icon to claim the item
	* Hint: use search bar to find partners
	        	</pre>
	        	<img src='/routesms/static/src/img/cliam_partner_1.png' class="partner_auction_image" />


	        	<pre>
	STEP 3 :
	* As you can see "Lester" is the 1st bidder of "3Gmotion".
	* Request status will be pending and more business managers can bid on "3Gmotion"
	
	        	</pre>
	        	<img src='/routesms/static/src/img/cliam_requested_1.png' class="partner_auction_image" />

	        	<pre>
	STEP 4 :
	* Other business manager can also claim  "3Gmotion" which is already bidded by "Lester"
	* Multiple business manager can bid on same partner
	
	
	        	</pre>
	        	<img src='/routesms/static/src/img/cliam_partner_2.png' class="partner_auction_image" />	        	


	        	<pre>
	STEP 5 :
	* Now you can see "3Gmotion" bidded by 2 business manager
	* Request to claim status is pending and all requests has been pushed to accounts department for approval
	
	
	        	</pre>
	        	<img src='/routesms/static/src/img/cliam_requested_2.png' class="partner_auction_image" />
	        	
	        	<pre>	        	

	STEP 6 :
	* Account user can track the bidded items
	* Winner of auction per item will be decided internally.Sales team and accounts team has to cordinate 
	internally to decide the winner
	* Account user has to follow Odoo BM swapping process to transfer partner to winner's account
	
	        	</pre>
	        	<img src='/routesms/static/src/img/check_bid_request.png' class="partner_auction_image" />	        	

			<h3>Contact Us For Queries:</h3>
			<h4>
				Email:shashank.verma@bistacloud.com<br></br>
				Skype:bista_shashank<br></br>
				Ext:696
			</h4>	      	
	       </div>
		<img src='/routesms/static/src/img/goodluck.jpg' class="partner_auction_image" />
        </div>
    </t>
</templates>
